

## PROFILE | PROFIL

Halo, saya Dody Prakarsa, kemampuan saya di bidang I.T adalah fullstack web developement dan I.T support specialist, saya mampu membuat situs web baru dengan berbagai framework javascript ataupun tanpa framework / vanilla javascript.

Hello, my name Dody Prakarsa, my ability in I.T field is fullstack website development and I.T support specialist, I can create a new website with various javascript frameworks or without a framework / vanilla javascript.

## **CONTACT | KONTAK**

#### PHONE:

+6283152699011

#### **WEBSITE:**

dodyprakarsa.github.io/portofolio

#### **EMAIL:**

dodyprakarsa@hotmail.com dontris@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES | KEGEMARAN**

Programming
Drone Pilot
Internet of Thing (IOT)
Swimming

# DODY PRAKARSA

I.T Support

# **EDUCATION | PENDIDIKAN**

#### **Mulawarman University**

2002 - 2003

Associate's Degree / D1

**Technician & Computer Programming** 

# **WORK EXPERIENCE | PENGALAMAN PEKERJAAN**

#### CV. Teras Hijau I.T Support Assistant

2020

Administration Virtual Machine AWS EC2 Build Frontend & Backend company private website Maintenance & Troubleshooting Cisco Router

#### PT. Naura Libra Jaya I.T Support Assistant

2017-2019

Administration Virtual Machine Google Cloud Compute Engine Build Frontend & Backend company private website

# Kantor Pertanahan Kota Samarinda I.T Support Assistant

2014-2016

Maintenance & Troubleshooting Dell Server Intel Xeon E5 Administration Windows Server 2012 R2 Datacenter

## **SKILLS | KEMAMPUAN**

HTML/CSS
Javascript
CCNA Network Engineer
AWS Cloud Practitioner
Microsoft Azure Administrator
I.T Support Specialist